befunkies.com 2014-10-12

# Privacy Policy

## **PRIVACY POLICY**

This Privacy Policy applies to any visitor or user (hereinafter referred to as “You”) of the website located at www.Befunkies.com and any websites (singularly and collectively, “the Site”) that Acorda Infotech Pvt. Ltd. (AIPL) Company or its subsidiaries (singularly and collectively, “AIPL”) own and control Befunkies.com is sensitive to the issue of confidentiality in online dealings and is committed to protecting individual privacy. This Privacy Policy is intended to inform users about the general approach AIPL uses in collecting, using and disseminating user information via the Site. This Privacy policy is subject to the terms of the Site Policy (User agreement) of Befunkies.com. This policy is effective from the date and time a user registers with Befunkies.com by filling up the Registration form and accepting the terms and conditions laid out in the Site Policy.

**What Personally Identifiable Information May Be Collected:**

At Befunkies.com, it is our policy to create website content that requires minimal collection of personally identifiable information from our visitors. However, to respond to your requests or to enable you to register or to use certain features of this Site, we may request personally identifiable information from you including, but not limited to, your name, home address, email address and/or telephone number. For a personalized browsing experience, Befunkies.com may collect personal information from you. Additionally some of our websites may require you to complete a registration form or seek some information from you. When you let us have your preferences, we will be able to deliver or allow you to access the most relevant information that meets your end.

When you visit our website the following information will automatically be processed and this solely for the use of this association:

1\. our business purposes and this may include the viewing or advertising of residential or commercial real estate buy/sale/rental properties or to use of associated services  
2\. analytical purposes, data usage  
3\. improving the Website, or your user experience  
4\. providing targeted advertisements to you

When we do collect personally identifiable information, we will only keep it until that particular activity (or set of activities) is complete. Generally, your personally identifiable information will not be given out to third parties not affiliated with Befunkies.com, however, from time to time we may transfer, disclose or share your personally identifiable information with third parties who may be engaged by us specifically to handle and deliver certain online activities. Such parties will have access to your personally identifiable information needed to perform these functions, but may not use it for other purposes.

Our Site may provide links to other websites that may have their own information collection practices. To the extent that you provide personally identifiable information to websites that link to or from our Site, different rules may apply to the use and disclosure of your personally identifiable information. To the extent that the Site includes third-party advertisements, the privacy policy of the advertiser providing the advertisement will govern the use of your personally identifiable information collected during your access to the advertisement. Befunkies.com does not control linking practices of advertisers or sponsors and does not monitor or claim responsibility for any content or privacy practices of such websites. Once you have clicked on an advertisement and have left our Site, you must read the privacy policy of the advertiser or sponsor to see how your personally identifiable information will be handled.  
From time to time, we make the e-mail addresses of those who access our site available to other reputable organizations whose products or services we think you might find interesting. If you do not want us to share your e-mail address with other companies or organizations, please let us know by emailing us at the address provided below.  
Persons who supply us with their telephone numbers on-line may receive telephone or text message contact from us with information regarding new products and services or upcoming events. If you do not wish to receive such telephone calls or text messages, please let us know by sending us e-mail at the below address.

**Other Types of Information That May Be Collected:**

**1\. IP Addresses**  
An Internet protocol address, or IP address, is automatically assigned to your computer when you access the Internet, and is used by web servers to identify your computer. When you access our Site, we may log your IP address, however, your identity will remain anonymous to us. We log the IP addresses for system administration and for auditing the use of our Site. We may also use IP addresses to collect statistical information for marketing and other purposes.  
**2\. Cookies or Tracers**  
From time to time, we may place information on your computer to allow us to identify you. This information is known as a “cookie”. We will only use cookies to view information on User’s computer’s hard drive that was placed there by a cookie from our Site, such as your preferences or which pages you have visited on the Site. However, a cookie will not allow our Site to learn any personally identifiable information that you have not otherwise disclosed (except as described below). By understanding how and when our visitors use the Site, we can continually improve our Site, as well as our products and services. If you wish to disable cookies, your browser can be reset to refuse all cookies or indicate when a cookie is being sent.  
In some instances, we use tracking scripts or "tracers" that recognize a unique identifier from a cookie placed on your hard drive by another website. These are used by Befunkies.com solely to gauge the success of our own advertising. For instance, we may use a tracer to determine whether you visit our employment pages after visiting a resume or career site where Befunkies.com placed a banner ad. We do not use tracers to gather information on your use of the Internet unrelated to Befunkies.com. Please note that Befunkies.com does not use tracers to determine your personally identifiable information, and you remain anonymous.  
**3\. Web Beacons:**  
Web beacons are small files that we may place on our Site, which count the number of unique users that have visited a specific page on the Site and the number of times a given page has been displayed. This information is collected only in the aggregate and is generally not linked to any personally identifiable information.  
**4\. What happens if I register?**  
Registration may be allowed or required on the Site. Please refer to the agreements and policies applicable to the Site for which you provide registration information in order to assure that you understand the applicable privacy practices. Befunkies.com may collect registration data in order to monitor compliance with this Privacy Policy and to set up access permissions to certain other pages on the Site.

**Use of Information:**

**a. Use and Sharing of Information**  
Befunkies.com and its affiliates may use and disclose your personally identifiable information only as set forth herein. Anonymous data collected using cookies and web beacons may be analyzed in the aggregate to determine collective user characteristics, to understand user traffic patterns, sales information and user behaviour on the Site. Such information also may be shared in the aggregate with third parties for advertising purposes, to enhance our Site, to enhance our products and services, and to analyze how and where best to use our resources.  
**b. Monitoring and Compliance**  
Although Befunkies.com is under no obligation to monitor the Site, we may monitor, store, review and disclose to third parties any information, including your personally identifiable information, obtained on or through the Site as may be needed or requested to satisfy any applicable governmental law, regulation, investigation or proceeding. Additionally, we may use IP addresses to identify a particular user if we believe it is needed to enforce compliance with these terms or to protect our company, employees, Site, or customers.

**Transaction Security Policy:**

While Befunkies.com tries to prevent third party, non-affiliate access to personally identifiable information, you should keep in mind that data transmission over the Internet is not 100% secure and any information disclosed online can potentially be collected and used other than by the intended recipient. In view of the foregoing, Befunkies.com cannot warrant that your personally identifiable information will not be disclosed to or accessed by parties other than those authorized under this Privacy Policy.  
The information we collect from you, will be stored in a safe and secure manner in our data centre. We shall restrict the access to your information unless required to process your service requests. If at any time you share credit card information with Us, We shall employ industry standard encryption techniques such as the Secure Socket Layer (SSL) to protect the same.  
While we will do our bit for the protection of your information, as a user of the Website You have a responsibility to ensure data security. You should use the Website in a responsible manner and should not share your username or password with any person.

**Updates to Your Information:**

At your request, Befunkies.com will make reasonable efforts to update, change or delete any personally identifiable information you have provided via the Site. In order to enforce the terms of this Privacy Policy, resolve disputes, or provide information to satisfy applicable governmental laws, regulations, investigations or proceedings, we may need to retain your personally identifiable information in our files. Additionally, your personally identifiable information may be retained in residual back-up files that are a function of our network’s back-up systems.

**Advertisements on Befunkies.com:**

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email  
address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. ****

**Age restrictions:**

To use this Website you should be of 18 years of age or older. If you are not of the requisite age we will not provide any information. If it comes to our attention that any information pertains to an individual under the age of 18 years, such information will, irrespective of its nature, be deleted without any notice.

**Changes to this Privacy Policy:**

If there are any changes to this privacy policy, we will replace this page with an updated version. It is therefore in your own interest to check the "Privacy Policy" page any time you access our web site so as to be aware of any changes which may occur from time to time.

**Your Consent:**

By using the Website and/ or by providing your information, you consent to the collection and use of the information you disclose on the Website in accordance with this Privacy Policy, including but not limited to Your consent for sharing your information as per this privacy policy.

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page so that you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it.

**Grievance:**

In accordance with Information Technology Act 2000 and rules made there under, for any Grievance :

Mr. Sanjeev

Acorda Infotech Pvt. Ltd.

GF-12A, Indra Prakash Building,

21 Barakhamba Road, New Delhi- 110001

Phone: (+91) 11-41519275

Time: 10.00 AM to 6.00 PM

**Feedback/ Questions:**

If you have any questions or concerns regarding Befunkies.com’s privacy policy, please contact us at [info@befunkies.com](mailto:info@befunkies.com)
